GUNJAN JAGWANI

Chartered Accountant

+(91) - 7049407328 •

cagunjankhiyani@gmail.com •

linkedin.com/in/gunjan-jagwani-64837a1a5 •

29-04-1991 •

OBJECTIVE ·····

Result oriented professional with appx 10 years of experience in accounting & finance operations, reporting, taxation and compliance and seeking a challenging position where I can utilize my extensive experience in financial management and accounting to contribute to the success and growth of the organization.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Wells Fargo International Solutions Private Limited

Financial Accountant, 09/2022 - Present

- Provided General Ledger support and analysis inclusive of period-end financial close responsibilities
- Responsible for posting statistical, interest rate swap, expense accrual and reversal kind of monthly journal entries on a timely basis and by applying all required controls
- Gather, review and monitor data from the general ledger, unit reports and various financial systems to perform financial control functions
- Worked on monthly intercompany reconciliation and collaborated with cross functional teams to resolve discrepancies and posting of respective journal entries
- Prepare and review account and balance sheet reconciliations to ensure that the balances in the ledger match with supporting documentation and sub-ledgers
- Having experience of assessing loan modification from qualitative and quantitative aspect
- Worked on Regulatory and 10-Q/K SEC Reporting to ensure accurate and timely financial reporting in compliance with accounting principles and regulations
- Reviewed securitization deals and works for creation of Special Purpose Entity in SPE database

Anil Industries Katni Private Limited

Account manager, 06/2019 - 09/2022

- Preparation & maintenance of statutory books of accounts and administering the finalization of year-end financial statements of Co
- Reconciliation of Accounts and periodic accounts checking of the Co. and group companies
- Prepared fixed asset schedule as per Income Tax Act and Companies Act and posted respective journal entries
- Assisted in preparation of Debit and Credit Notes
- Handled statutory compliances related to MCA, TDS, GST, FSSAI for Co
- Prepared various reports required by the management
- Income tax working experience of family members of the group

Gunjan Jagwani & Associates, Chartered Accountant Firm

Chartered Accountant, 08/2016 - 05/2019

- Worked on preparation and filing of Income tax returns of individuals and firms
- Prepared and submitted GSTR-1, GSTR-3B
- Tax Audit and GST Audit
- Preparation and finalisation of financial statements of proprietorship and partnership firms
- Worked on preparation of project report for bank loan
- Provided attestation services

Balaji Fashion, Group Unit of Ethix Clothing

Account manager, 12/2012 - 06/2015

- Assisted and worked with IT team for implementation of ERP in finance module.
- Had experience of reviewing, assessing and negotiating terms of various contracts like lease agreement, franchise agreement etc.
- Worked on compliance related to VAT and CST

EDUCATION

Chartered Accountant, May 2012

The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India

Bachelor of Commerce, July 2011

DAVV University, Indore (M.P.)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Sound knowledge of Microsoft Office, with a focus on Excel
- Proficient in Essbase, Tally, Dataman, Genesis
- US GAAP